megarelease.net 2014-04-15

# Privacy Policy

**Mega Release Privacy Policy**

**Mega Release Privacy Statement**  
This privacy statement is valid for Megarelease. Where Megarelease refers to Megarelease.com.au 

Protecting our customer privacy is important to Megarelease. Following statement/terms will help you to understand how our affiliate or Megarelease collects, uses and secure the personal information you provide to us on our site.

  * Information is being collected. We keep track of the pages the customer is visiting and for how long duration, clicks etc for future marketing and improvements.
  * We collect some personal info like name, email addresses using two way optin email subscribers to provide our subscribers with latest news, freebies, and discounts offers available on time to time 
  * We don't sell or rent your email and other personal info to third party marketing companies
  * We use "cookies" for collecting consumer information for improving our website marketing, user friendliness and click through rate.
  * Our Affiliate company process all the online payments using their secure server and we are nowhere responsible for any loss of your personal information like credit card, personal details etc.
  * You can easily opt out from our our mailing list at anytime.

All inquires related to your order and other stuff is handled by our Affiliate partners only, we will no way provide any updates on your order etc

You can contact us by a contact us form if you find any discrepenacy or find any issues with our website funcationality.  
All customer service cocncers will be taken care by our affiliate partners only.

Our All Affiliate partners have utilised latest SSL ( Secure Socket Layers) protocol to encrypts your personal information being transferred over the internet.

We can change to our privacy policy and you can see our latest amended priacy policy over here

Privacy Policy latest update: 22 March 2013
